<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mixed Origin on madewhere</title><link>https://madewhere.co/tags/mixed-origin/</link><description>Recent content in Mixed Origin on madewhere</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>madewhere Contributors</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 14:51:25 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://madewhere.co/tags/mixed-origin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Estwing</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/estwing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 14:51:25 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/estwing/</guid><description>Estwing is a tool manufacturer, specializing in hammers. A large number of their products are USA-made, with exceptions being their specialty fiberglass and plastic hammers.</description></item><item><title>Channellock</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/channellock/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 14:43:30 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/channellock/</guid><description>Channellock is a tool manufacturer, probably best known for their channel-locking pliers. They offer a variety of gripping tools, made in the USA.
Unfortunately not all of their products are USA-made, but those that are carry a prominent label. Those that are not do not denote their origin in an obvious manner.</description></item><item><title>Tanner Goods</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/tanner-goods/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 14:10:08 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/tanner-goods/</guid><description>Tanner Goods is a leather goods manufacturer based in Portland, OR. They produce a range of belts, wallets, bags, and other accessories.
While Tanner&amp;rsquo;s core products are produced in the USA, they do not exclusively carry US-made products.</description></item><item><title>Oral-B</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/oral-b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 10:27:12 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/oral-b/</guid><description>Oral-B manufactures a number of their toothbrush lines in Europe; any that fall under the &amp;ldquo;Pro&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Professional Care&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;Triumph&amp;rdquo; lines. However they do not prominently list the origin of each product, and details can be difficult to find.</description></item><item><title>Le Creuset</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/le-cruset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 21:00:57 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/le-cruset/</guid><description>Le Creuset is a famous cast iron bakeware manufacturer. Probably best known for their Dutch ovens, but they make a considerable variety of kitchen products.
While many of their cast iron products are made in France, this does not extend to all of their product lines, which are made in a variety of countries.</description></item><item><title>Mission Workshop</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/mission-workshop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 21:02:25 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/mission-workshop/</guid><description>Mission Workshop is a San Francisco-based maker of bags and technical clothing; they focused mostly on bike gear, but have since diversified into more technical wear. Much of their technical gear isn&amp;rsquo;t made in the USA, so be sure to check on a product-by-product basis.</description></item><item><title>Heath Ceramics</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/heath-ceramics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 22:52:42 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/heath-ceramics/</guid><description>Heath Ceramics is primarily known for ceramic goods which they make in their California factory. They&amp;rsquo;ve recently started producing other products, like flatware. They also carry a significant number of other items which seem carefully selected, but haven&amp;rsquo;t been fully evaluated.
See their vendor page for more information.</description></item><item><title>Red Wing</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/red-wing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 13:19:50 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/red-wing/</guid><description>Red Wing is a shoe manufacturer based in Minnesota. They offer a &amp;ldquo;heritage&amp;rdquo; line of shoes which are fully made in the USA. They also offer a &amp;ldquo;work&amp;rdquo; line of shoes and boots which are of varying origins and should be evaluated individually.</description></item><item><title>Demeyere</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/demeyere/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/demeyere/</guid><description>Demeyere offers a wide range of made in belgium cookware.</description></item><item><title>Staub</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/staub/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/staub/</guid><description>Staub is a cookware manufacturer specializing in cast iron pans and dutch ovens.</description></item><item><title>Wüsthof</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/wusthof/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/wusthof/</guid><description>Wüsthof offers a wide range of kitchen knives. Many are made in Germany—such as their &amp;ldquo;Classic&amp;rdquo; line—but they sell some lines to big box retailers which are not. Similarly they offer other kitchen utensils which are of unknown origin.</description></item><item><title>Zojirushi</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/zojirushi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/zojirushi/</guid><description>Zojirushi is probably best known for their rice cookers, but they make a considerable line of small appliances including water boilers and bread makers, a number of which are made in Japan. They also make a line of vacuum mugs and containers, but their country of origin varies.</description></item><item><title>ZWILLING J.A. Henckels</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/zwilling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/zwilling/</guid><description>ZWILLING J.A. Henckles is the parent company of several brands, including Staub and Demeyere.</description></item><item><title>All-Clad</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/all-clad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/all-clad/</guid><description>All-Clad is known for their clad cookware, but the also offer utensils and various kitchen goods. Unfortunately they have begun outsourcing some manufacturing to China—usually identifiable by significantly lower prices—but many of their products are still manufactured in the USA.</description></item><item><title>Cambro</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/cambro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/cambro/</guid><description>Cambro is best known for their food storage products, which are popular in food service but also excellent for home. The vast majority of these are made in the USA.
Cambro focuses on commercial markets and doesn&amp;rsquo;t sell direct to consumers, but their products can be found on WebstaurantStore.</description></item><item><title>Thermoworks</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/thermoworks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/thermoworks/</guid><description>Thermoworks primary product is handheld fast-read digital thermometers for cooking use. Their flagship Thermapen line is made in England.
Products which are made in England are explicitly market on product pages.</description></item><item><title>Vollrath</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/vollrath/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/vollrath/</guid><description>Vollrath is a cookware and bakeware company, focused on commercial kitchen. A substantial portion of their goods are made in the USA, including their &amp;ldquo;Jacob&amp;rsquo;s Pride&amp;rdquo; line of clad cookware which is relatively inexpensive vs other clad lines.
While Vollrath doesn&amp;rsquo;t sell directly to consumers, their goods are carried by WebstaurantStore which lists a prominent &amp;ldquo;Made in USA&amp;rdquo; badge on relevant products.</description></item></channel></rss>