<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>USA on madewhere</title><link>https://madewhere.co/origins/usa/</link><description>Recent content in USA on madewhere</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>madewhere Contributors</copyright><atom:link href="https://madewhere.co/origins/usa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kamik</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/kamik/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 18:37:00 -0900</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/kamik/</guid><description>Kamik is a Canadian shoe manufacturer who continues to manufacture some of their lines in the USA and Canada, most notably their &amp;ldquo;Heritage 1898&amp;rdquo; women’s and men’s lines. Products that are US- or Canada-made are clearly marked in the product descriptions, however other products do not list their country of manufacture. Some are known to be made in India.</description></item><item><title>Wilcox</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/wilcox/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 20:27:03 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/wilcox/</guid><description>Wilcox is a garden tool manufacturer, specializing in digging tools.</description></item><item><title>Marley's Monsters</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/marleys-monsters/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 19:53:26 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/marleys-monsters/</guid><description>Marley&amp;rsquo;s Monsters provides a wide range of reusable cloth products—towels, napkins, coffee filters—meant to reduce use of paper disposables. They produce their goods in Eugene, Oregon.</description></item><item><title>LloydPans</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/lloydpans/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 22:55:02 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/lloydpans/</guid><description>LloydPans is a kitchenware manufacturer, offering fry pans, baking sheets, and pizza pans, made in the USA.</description></item><item><title>White Industries</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/white-industries/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:36:08 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/white-industries/</guid><description>White Industries is a bicycle component manufacturer based in California.</description></item><item><title>Chris King</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/chris-king/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:28:27 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/chris-king/</guid><description>Chris King is a bicycle components manufacturer based in Portland, Oregon.</description></item><item><title>Dehen 1920</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/dehen-1920/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 14:29:03 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/dehen-1920/</guid><description>Dehen 1920 is a clothing manufacturer based in Portland, Oregon.</description></item><item><title>Vitamix</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/vitamix/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 14:13:19 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/vitamix/</guid><description>Vitamix manufacturers high performance commercial and home blenders out of their Ohio factory. Products which are made in the USA are clearly labeled on individual pages.</description></item><item><title>USA Pan</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/usa-pan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 19:30:37 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/usa-pan/</guid><description>USA Pan makes a distinctive style of baking pan, offering the usual suspects: baking sheets, muffin tins, loaf pans, etc.</description></item><item><title>Epicurean</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/epicurean/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 20:23:15 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/epicurean/</guid><description>Epicurean is a USA-based manufacturer of composite cutting surfaces. They have a wide range of cutting boards and other kitchen accessories. All products are made in the USA.</description></item><item><title>Estwing</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/estwing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 14:51:25 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/estwing/</guid><description>Estwing is a tool manufacturer, specializing in hammers. A large number of their products are USA-made, with exceptions being their specialty fiberglass and plastic hammers which are made in Taiwan.</description></item><item><title>Channellock</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/channellock/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 14:43:30 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/channellock/</guid><description>Channellock is a tool manufacturer, probably best known for their channel-locking pliers. They offer a variety of gripping tools, made in the USA.
Products which are USA-made carry a prominent label. Other items may not specify their origins on product pages.</description></item><item><title>Tanner Goods</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/tanner-goods/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 14:10:08 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/tanner-goods/</guid><description>Tanner Goods is a leather goods manufacturer based in Portland, OR. They produce a range of belts, wallets, bags, and other accessories.
While Tanner&amp;rsquo;s core products are produced in the USA, they do not exclusively carry US-made products.</description></item><item><title>D'Addario</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/d-addario/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 11:27:41 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/d-addario/</guid><description>D&amp;rsquo;Addario is a manufacturer of musical instrument strings and accessories, which makes all of their products in the USA.</description></item><item><title>Field Notes</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/field-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 11:08:50 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/field-notes/</guid><description>Field Notes is a pocket-carry notebook manufacturer, based in Chicago, IL.</description></item><item><title>Lawn Chair USA</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/lawn-chair-usa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 11:04:10 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/lawn-chair-usa/</guid><description>Lawn Chair USA manufactures classic styled lawn chairs in the USA, as their name suggests.</description></item><item><title>Benchmade</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/benchmade/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 10:56:02 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/benchmade/</guid><description>Benchmade is an American knife manufacturer, which produces a wide range of knives in their Oregon City, OR factory. Since discontinuing their off-shore manufacturing in 2010, all of their products are USA-made.</description></item><item><title>Chicago Metallic</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/chicago-metallic/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 22:40:03 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/chicago-metallic/</guid><description>Chicago Metallic is a bakeware company focused on commercial markets. Their site asserts that all products are made in the USA, with global materials.
While Chicago Metallic doesn&amp;rsquo;t sell directly to consumers, they are carried by WebstaurantStore.</description></item><item><title>Rogue Territory</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/rogue-territory/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 21:15:54 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/rogue-territory/</guid><description>Rogue Territory is a clothing brand, manufactured primarily in California; they make denim jeans, jackets, shirts, and accessories.</description></item><item><title>North St.</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/north-st/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 21:09:28 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/north-st/</guid><description>North St. is a cycling bag maker in Portland, Oregon. They make backpacks, panniers, handlebar bags, etc. They&amp;rsquo;ve also started making more hiking focused gear. Many of their products are made to order.</description></item><item><title>Mission Workshop</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/mission-workshop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 21:02:25 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/mission-workshop/</guid><description>Mission Workshop is a San Francisco-based maker of bags and technical clothing; they focused mostly on bike gear, but have since diversified into more technical wear.</description></item><item><title>Heath Ceramics</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/heath-ceramics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 22:52:42 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/heath-ceramics/</guid><description>Heath Ceramics is primarily known for ceramic goods which they make in their California factory. They&amp;rsquo;ve recently started producing other products, like flatware. They also carry a significant number of other items which seem carefully selected, but haven&amp;rsquo;t been comprehensively evaluated.
See their vendor page for more information.</description></item><item><title>Graf Lantz</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/graf-lantz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 22:51:55 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/graf-lantz/</guid><description>Graf Lantz is a Los Angeles manufacturer. They make a large number of items for the home and office, as well as bags and other accessories; it spans items like desk mats, sunglass cases, tote bags, face masks, etc.</description></item><item><title>John Boos</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/john-boos/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 20:39:38 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/john-boos/</guid><description>John Boos &amp;amp; Co. are a butcher block manufacturer, known by the &amp;ldquo;Boos Block&amp;rdquo; logo burned into the side of their products. In addition to counter top butcher blocks, they also make standalone kitchen furniture (such as islands) and installer materials, like full butcher block counter tops.</description></item><item><title>Corelle</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/corelle/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 17:05:40 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/corelle/</guid><description>Corelle is well known for their distinctive glass dishware, which is made in Corning, NY.</description></item><item><title>Sherrill Manufacturing</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/sherrill-manufacturing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 13:48:01 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/sherrill-manufacturing/</guid><description>Sherrill Manufacturing is the parent company of several brands listed below. They purchased the former Oneida Limited facilities, and continue making products in the USA.</description></item><item><title>Liberty Tabletop</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/liberty-tabletop/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 13:45:02 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/liberty-tabletop/</guid><description>Liberty Tabletop is a flatware manufacturer, which is a subsidiary of Sherrill Manufacturing.</description></item><item><title>Darn Tough</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/darn-tough/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 13:34:12 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/darn-tough/</guid><description>Darn Tough offers merino wool socks for a range of purposes; they are probably best known for their hiking sock, but offer more casual options as well. They are made in Vermont, and guaranteed for life .</description></item><item><title>Red Wing</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/red-wing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 13:19:50 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/red-wing/</guid><description>Red Wing is a shoe manufacturer based in Minnesota. They offer a &amp;ldquo;heritage&amp;rdquo; line of shoes which are fully made in the USA. They also offer a &amp;ldquo;work&amp;rdquo; line of shoes and boots which are of varying origins.</description></item><item><title>Fletchers' Mill</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/fletchers-mill/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/fletchers-mill/</guid><description>Fletchers' Mill is known for their pepper mills, but also offer a variety of wooden tools such as rolling pins, honey dippers, and etc.</description></item><item><title>Lamson</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/lamson/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/lamson/</guid><description>Lamson provides a wide variety of kitchen knives and tools, all made in their Massachusetts factory.</description></item><item><title>360 Cookware</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/360-cookware/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/360-cookware/</guid><description>360 Cookware makes various cookware, bakeware, flatware, and other utensils in the USA.</description></item><item><title>All-Clad</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/all-clad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/all-clad/</guid><description>All-Clad is known for their clad cookware, but the also offer utensils and various kitchen goods. Most of their core product line—pots, pans, and other cookware—is manufactured in the USA. Other products, such as utensils and appliances, have varying origins.</description></item><item><title>Cambro</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/cambro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/cambro/</guid><description>Cambro is best known for their food storage products, which are popular in food service but also excellent for home. The vast majority of these are made in the USA, at least for the USA market. They highlight all of their locations and purposes on their careers page, as well as the number of employees in each location.
Cambro focuses on commercial markets and doesn&amp;rsquo;t sell direct to consumers, but their products can be found on WebstaurantStore.</description></item><item><title>Solidteknics</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/solidteknics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/solidteknics/</guid><description>Solidteknics is a manufacturer with seemingly two independent arms: one in Australia, and one in the USA. They manufacture wrought iron cookware in each of these markets.</description></item><item><title>Vollrath</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/vollrath/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/vollrath/</guid><description>Vollrath is a cookware and bakeware company, focused on commercial kitchen. A substantial portion of their goods are made in the USA, including their &amp;ldquo;Jacob&amp;rsquo;s Pride&amp;rdquo; line of clad cookware.
While Vollrath doesn&amp;rsquo;t sell directly to consumers, their goods are carried by WebstaurantStore which lists a prominent &amp;ldquo;Made in USA&amp;rdquo; badge on relevant products.</description></item></channel></rss>