<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>China on madewhere</title><link>https://madewhere.co/origins/china/</link><description>Recent content in China on madewhere</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>madewhere Contributors</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 14:43:30 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://madewhere.co/origins/china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Channellock</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/channellock/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 14:43:30 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/channellock/</guid><description>Channellock is a tool manufacturer, probably best known for their channel-locking pliers. They offer a variety of gripping tools, made in the USA.
Unfortunately not all of their products are USA-made, but those that are carry a prominent label. Those that are not do not denote their origin in an obvious manner.</description></item><item><title>Le Creuset</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/le-cruset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 21:00:57 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/le-cruset/</guid><description>Le Creuset is a famous cast iron bakeware manufacturer. Probably best known for their Dutch ovens, but they make a considerable variety of kitchen products.
While many of their cast iron products are made in France, this does not extend to all of their product lines, which are made in a variety of countries.</description></item><item><title>All-Clad</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/all-clad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/all-clad/</guid><description>All-Clad is known for their clad cookware, but the also offer utensils and various kitchen goods. Unfortunately they have begun outsourcing some manufacturing to China—usually identifiable by significantly lower prices—but many of their products are still manufactured in the USA.</description></item><item><title>Cambro</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/cambro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/cambro/</guid><description>Cambro is best known for their food storage products, which are popular in food service but also excellent for home. The vast majority of these are made in the USA, at least for the USA market. They highlight all of their locations and purposes on their careers page, as well as the number of employees in each location.
Cambro focuses on commercial markets and doesn&amp;rsquo;t sell direct to consumers, but their products can be found on WebstaurantStore.</description></item><item><title>Thermoworks</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/thermoworks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/thermoworks/</guid><description>Thermoworks primary product is handheld fast-read digital thermometers for cooking use. Their flagship Thermapen line is made in England.
Products which are made in England are explicitly market on product pages.</description></item><item><title>Vollrath</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/vollrath/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/vollrath/</guid><description>Vollrath is a cookware and bakeware company, focused on commercial kitchen. A substantial portion of their goods are made in the USA, including their &amp;ldquo;Jacob&amp;rsquo;s Pride&amp;rdquo; line of clad cookware which is relatively inexpensive vs other clad lines.
While Vollrath doesn&amp;rsquo;t sell directly to consumers, their goods are carried by WebstaurantStore which lists a prominent &amp;ldquo;Made in USA&amp;rdquo; badge on relevant products.</description></item></channel></rss>