<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dinnerware on madewhere</title><link>https://madewhere.co/categories/dinnerware/</link><description>Recent content in Dinnerware on madewhere</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>madewhere Contributors</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 21:00:57 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://madewhere.co/categories/dinnerware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Le Creuset</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/le-cruset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 21:00:57 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/le-cruset/</guid><description>Le Creuset is a famous cast iron bakeware manufacturer. Probably best known for their Dutch ovens, but they make a considerable variety of kitchen products.
While many of their cast iron products are made in France, this does not extend to all of their product lines, which are made in a variety of countries.</description></item><item><title>Heath Ceramics</title><link>https://madewhere.co/vendors/heath-ceramics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 20:49:43 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/vendors/heath-ceramics/</guid><description>Heath Ceramics is primarily known for their ceramic products, but they also act as a vendor for a wide variety of items which appear to be from reasonable sources.
They list origin of products they carry prominently on individual product pages.</description></item><item><title>Heath Ceramics</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/heath-ceramics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 22:52:42 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/heath-ceramics/</guid><description>Heath Ceramics is primarily known for ceramic goods which they make in their California factory. They&amp;rsquo;ve recently started producing other products, like flatware. They also carry a significant number of other items which seem carefully selected, but haven&amp;rsquo;t been fully evaluated.
See their vendor page for more information.</description></item><item><title>Corelle</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/corelle/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 17:05:40 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/corelle/</guid><description>The Corelle style of glass dishware is ubiquitous and an American staple. It is still made in Corning, NY.</description></item><item><title>Duralex</title><link>https://madewhere.co/brands/duralex/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://madewhere.co/brands/duralex/</guid><description>Duralex is a manufacturer of glassware; they specialize in drinkware and dinnerware, and is known for its robustness. All of their glassware is made in France, and can be bought direct from their USA distribution.
In 2021 they were purchased by Pyrex, but while sharing a name with the American Pyrex (owned by Corning), Pyrex EU appears to be a different company.</description></item></channel></rss>